ILR School Extension Division Metropolitan District Office (New York, N.Y.), Figueroa, Maria, Papers /4354/004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Extension Division Metropolitan District Office (New York, N.Y.), Maria Figueroa Papers
1997-2014
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Figueroa, Maria
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Metropolitan District Office
/4354/004
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records, memoribilia.
This collection contain the files of Cornell University faculty member Maria Figueroa.
10606762
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
E. Parker, February 04, 2019
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 04, 2019
Biographical / Historical
Maria C. Figueroa is Director of Labor and Policy Research at the Worker Institute, Cornell University-School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Maria's work has involved applied research and technical assistance in the area of low wage and contingent (or precarious) work. She has worked in several projects commissioned by unions, employer groups, government agencies, and private foundations. Maria has more than 25 years of experience in labor and industry research, having worked as a senior analyst and researcher for national and international organizations, including the Teamsters Union and the United Nations.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4352: Lois Gray Collection of Training Materials /4068: ILR School Extension Division Metropolitan District Office, Anne Nelson Papers /4026: ILR School Metropolitan Office Extension Division Completed Questionnaires on Union Activity /4296: ILR School Extension Division Metropolitan District Office (New York, N.Y.) Training Manuals /4296 AV: ILR School Extension Division Metropolitan District Office (New York, N.Y.) Training Audio-Visual Materials /4321 AV: ILR School Smithers Institute Audio-Visual Materials /4354/004 AV: ILR School Extension Division Metropolitan District Office (New York, N.Y.), Maria Figueroa Audio-Visual Materials /4354/004 G: ILR School Extension Division Metropolitan District Office (New York, N.Y.), Maria Figueroa Graphics Collection /4354/004 P: ILR School Extension Division Metropolitan District Office (New York, N.Y.), Maria Figueroa Photographs 6446: 1199 Collections
Figueroa, Maria; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Metropolitan District Office; American Federation of Television and Radio Artists; Service Employees International Union. Local 1199 (New York, N.Y.); Local 1199 Drug, Hospital, and Health Care Employees Union (New York, N.Y.); Transport Workers Union of America
10606762
- Broadway Data (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Lois's Arts and Entertainment, Other (Box 1, Folder 2)
- 95th International Convention AFM of the United States and Canada - Riviera Hotel and Casino June 23-25 2003 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- New York City Central Labor Council, AFL-CIO (March 6, 2004) (Box 1, Folder 4)
- AFTRA 1937-1997 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Processed Fruits and Vegetables Industry (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Unions Forms (Box 1, Folder 7)
- National Code of Fair Practice for Commercial Radio Broadcasting 1994-1997 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- AFTRA Radio Recorded Commercials Contract 1997 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- AFTRA Radio Recorded Commercials Contract 2003 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Television Recorded Commercials Contract 2003 (AFTRA & ANA & AAAA) (Box 1, Folder 11)
- AFTRA Television Recorded Commercials Contract 1997 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- AFTRA National Code of Fair Practice for Sound Recording 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- AFTRA National Code of Fair Practice for Commercial Radio Broadcasting 1994-1997 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- The Construction Industry Partnership (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Union Guide to Quality Managed Care AFL-CIO (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Workers Unite Film Festival NYC (May 4-19, 2014) (Box 1, Folder 17)
- The Coalition of Kaiser Permanente Unions, AFL-CIO (October 1th, 2000) - National Agreement (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Inside Out September 18, 2000 - Unions at Kaiser - Coalition of Kaiser Permanente Unions - AFL-CIO (Box 1, Folder 19)
- 1199 Labor-Management Participation (Box 1, Folder 20)
- 1199 - Montefiore (Box 1, Folder 21)
- 1199 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Healthcare Industry Restructuring Research (January 23, 1997) (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Health Care in New York City - Patterns and Perspectives (James R. Tallon Jr.) Conference (December 12, 2000) (Box 1, Folder 24)
- By-Laws of the Transport Workers Union of Greater New York Local 100, AFL-CIO (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Collective Bargaining Agreement between League of Voluntary Hospitals and Homes of New York and 1199 SEIU (Box 1, Folder 26)
  Scope and Contents
  two booklets (July1, 1998- October 31, 2001) and (July 1, 1992 - June 30, 1995)
- Transport Workers Union of America, AFL-CIO, Constitution 2001 Edition (Box 1, Folder 27)
- WGA-ABC 1993-96 National Agreement (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Pinback Buttons (Box 1, Folder 29)
  two pinback buttons; (1) save the met, (2) I stand with nail salon workers